# Tomer Nov Full Stack Developer

Petach Tikva | 054-885-9596 | tomernov@outlook.com Github | LinkedIn | tomernoy.com

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm an autodidact dedicated developer, experienced maily in Flutter, JavaScript and Python programming with background in computer science and some management skills.

I've lived in China for about 13 years so I'm also fluent in Chinese.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Python, Django, Swift, Firebase, IOS, OOP, SQL, Javascript, Node.js, Dart, Flutter, Linux, MongoDB, AWS, REST APIs, HTML, CSS, SASS, HTMX, NGINX, Heroku, AliCloud.

### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS HIGHLIGHTS**

## DiamNet \*\* available on Google play and App store

A built from scratch full-stack cross-platform mobile app for the Diamond trading industry Writ ten in Flutter

- Front-end: Dart/Flutter, HTML/CSS.
- Back-end: Linux Restful API using Node is Express, MongoDB, NGINX, Websockets (live chats), reversed Proxies, load balancers, Alibaba Cloud (previously AWS and Azure), SMS auth, JWT, hashing, encryption algorithm, excel file uploads to app objects.

## **Jewelry Website**

Jewelry shop website i created for my final project using Django, HTML/CSS, SQLight, HTMX and deployed on Heroku also available on Github

## Kap & Roni

Nanobebe

A version of the game "snakes and ladders" but based on reaction speed instead of luck Written in Flutter

- Moving players dynamically with Flutter Animations
- State management with providers

## **Interval Countdown Timer**

Exercise interval countdown timer I built for my first 2 day Hackathon project - Preview HTML/CSS, JS

#### **Temporary Email Generator**

Desktop app that generates temporary emails for any registrations online quickly with a local inbox written in Python with Tkinter GUI

### **EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS**

## **Mobile & Front-End Development**

Ramat-Gan, Israel 2022, June - current

Flutter, Swift IOS, JavaScript, Firebase, HTML/CSS, Azure DevOps.

## Front-End Development Instructor

Tel-Aviv, Israel

Developers Institute

JavaScript, HTML/CSS.

## **Mobile Application Developer**

Xiamen, China

DiamNet LTD - Building DiamNet\*\* and uploading on Google play / App store

2016 - 2020

Dart/Flutter, JavaScript, Node.js Express REST API, Linux, MongoDB, SQL, HTML/CSS, NGINX, AliCloud. 2020

2016 -

2022

## Office Manager

Xiamen, China

Julius Klein - Eliaz Diamonds

Negotiating expensive diamond trade deals on international stock with high-end clients

2012 - 2015

Handling logistics of products supply to stores across China safely

**Translator**Embassy Of China - Israel

2009 - 2011

• Translating and handling confidential information regarding the consulate services in Israel

## **EDUCATION**

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript programTel-Aviv, IsraelDevelopers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp2021Python, JavaScript, DOM, HTML/CSS, OOP, SQL, Heroku, Github, Data Science.10/2021 - Present

## **LANGUAGES**

Hebrew - native speaker, English - fluent, Chinese - fluent